A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, 1988-1989
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia 1988-1989
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.911
This collection consists of 25,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 1991 August 26.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by Robert O'Neil, the President of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: general files, 1988-1989; seldom used permanent files, 1980-1991; ad hoc committee files, 1982-1991; administrative committees, 1980-1989; and, Robert O'Neil's speeches files, 1987-1989.
Organization
Series I: General Files, 1988-1989 Boxes 1-54
Series II: Seldom Used Permanent Files, 1980-1991 Boxes 55-59
Series III: Ad Hoc Committees Files, 1982-1991 Boxes 59-60
Series IV: Administrative Committees Files, 1980-1989 Boxes 61-65
Series V: Robert O'Neil's Speech Files, 1985-1990 Boxes 66-71
Series VI: Restricted Materials, 1987-1989 Boxes 72-74
Contents List
- Series I: General Records
  - "A" Miscellaneous (5 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Administration--General 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Computing Services 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--General (Restricted) 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--Law (Restricted) 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--Medical 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Afro-American Affairs--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Afro-American Affairs--Woodson Institute 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association--General and Board of Managers (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Alumni and Friends Letter 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - American Association of University Professors 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - American Bar Association (4 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - American Council on Education--General 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - Annual Reports 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - Anthropology 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - Applications for Positions (A-Z) (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - Architecture--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - Art--Bayly Museum 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - Asian Studies--General (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - Associated Western Universities--General 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Colleges--General 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - Association of American Universities--General (4 folders) 1988 Dec-1989 Jun (Box 5)
  - Association of American Universities--Executive Committee 1988-1989 (Box 5)
  - Association of American Universities--Membership Meeting (New Orleans) (2 folders) 1988 Oct (Box 6)
  - Association of American Universities--Washington, D.C. (3 folders) 1988 Apr (Box 6)
  - Association of Governing Boards--General 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Association of Research Libraries--General 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges--General 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Astronomy--General (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--General (3 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--ACC 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--CFA 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--NCAA 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--Personnel (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Athletics--Finances (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Attorney General (State)--General 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Auditor-Internal--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts--General 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - "B" Miscellaneous (1-3 of 6) 1988-1989 (Box 8)
  - "B" Miscellaneous (4-6 of 6) 1988-1989 (Box 9)
  - Biology--General 1988-1989 (Box 9)
  - Birdwood--General 1988-1989 (Box 9)
  - Business and Finance--General 1988-1989 (Box 9)
  - Business and Finance--Vice President Planning Group (VPPG) 1988-1989 (Box 9)
  - "C" Miscellaneous (1 of 9) 1988-1989 (Box 9)
  - "C" Miscellaneous (2-6 of 9) 1988-1989 (Box 10)
  - "C" Miscellaneous (7-9 of 9) 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - Career Planning and Placement--General 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - Cavalier Daily--General 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT) (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 12)
  - Center for Public Service--General 1988-1989 (Box 12)
  - Charlottesville, City of--General 1988-1989 (Box 12)
  - Charlottesville, City of--Planning & Coordination Council 1988-1989 (Box 12)
  - Chemistry--General 1988-1989 (Box 12)
  - China--General 1988-1989 (Box 12)
  - Civil Rights--General 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Classics--General 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Clinch Valley College--General 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - College of Arts and Sciences--General 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - College Board--General 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Commerce--General 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Community Colleges--General 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Comptroller (State) 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Condolences "A-Z" 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Congress--General (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Consortia--General 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Consortia--Capital (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Consortia--Central Virginia 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Consortia--North Virginia 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - Consortia--Tidewater 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Consortia--Valley 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Consortia--Western 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Continuing Education--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Council of Presidents--General 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Council of Presidents--MTG plans 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Council of South, Universities 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Council on Post Secondary Accreditation--General (COPA) 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Council on Post Secondary Accreditation--Educational Quality and Accreditation 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Council on Post Secondary Accreditation--Task Force on Educational Quality (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 14)
  - Duke University (3 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - "D" Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - "D" Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1988-1989 (Box 16)
  - Darden Graduate School of Business Administration--General 1988-1989 (Box 16)
  - Darden Business Sponsors--General 1988-1989 (Box 16)
  - Dean's Meetings 1988-1989 (Box 16)
  - Development--General (1 of 3) 1988-1989 (Box 16)
  - Development--General (2-3 of 3) 1988-1989 (Box 17)
  - Development--Internal Development Group (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 17)
  - Development--"Perspectives" 1988-1989 (Box 17)
  - Drama--General 1988-1989 (Box 18)
  - "E" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 18)
  - Economics--General 1988-1989 (Box 18)
  - Education--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 18)
  - Engineering and Applied Science--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - Engineering and Applied Science Development Committee (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - Engineering and Buildings (State)--General 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - English--General 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - Enrollment--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - Environmental Sciences--General 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - Equal Opportunity Office--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 20)
  - "F" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 6) 1988-1989 (Box 20)
  - "F" Miscellaneous (3-6 of 6) 1988-1989 (Box 21)
  - Faculty--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - Faculty Letter 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences--General 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - Financial Aid to Students--General 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - Food Services--General 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - French-General 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - "G" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 23)
  - General Assembly--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 23)
  - General Assembly--House Appropriations (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 24)
  - General Assembly--Legislative Summaries 1988-1989 (Box 24)
  - General Services (State)--General 1988-1989 (Box 24)
  - German--General 1988-1989 (Box 24)
  - Gifts and Grants--"A-E" (4 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 24)
  - Gifts and Grants--"F-K" (3 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 25)
  - Gifts and Grants--"L-R" (1 of 3) 1988-1989 (Box 25)
  - Gifts and Grants--"L-R" (2-3 of 3) 1988-1989 (Box 26)
  - Gifts and Grants--"S-Z" (1-3 of 4) 1988-1989 (Box 26)
  - Gifts and Grants--"S-Z" (4 of 4) 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs--General 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Governmental Relations--General 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Governor--General 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government--Administration 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government--Commerce and Resources (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government--Decentralization Task Force (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government--Education 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government--Finance 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government--Health and Human Resources 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government--Natural Resources 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government--Task Force on Science and Technology (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government--Transportation and Public Safety 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government--Virginia-Israel Commission (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Government--Washington Liaison Office 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences--General 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - "H" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 6) 1988-1989 (Box 27)
  - "H" Miscellaneous (3-6 of 6) 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Harrison Foundation 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - History--General 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Honor System--General (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Housing--General 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - "I" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Information Technology (State)--General 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Institute of Government--General (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Institutional Planning and Studies--General 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs--General (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - International Studies--General 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - International Studies 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - "J" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Jefferson Memorial Foundation, Thomas--General 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Jefferson Scholars Program--General 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Jeffersonian Restoration Advisory Board--General 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Jeffersonian Restoration Advisory Board--Committee--Newsletter 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review--Commission (JLARC) 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - "K" Miscellaneous (1 of 3) 1988-1989 (Box 30)
  - "K" Miscellaneous (2-3 of 3) 1988-1989 (Box 31)
  - Kluge, John 1988-1989 (Box 31)
  - "L" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 31)
  - Law--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 32)
  - Lawn Use Policy (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 32)
  - Legal Advisor--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 32)
  - Library--General 1988-1989 (Box 32)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1988-1989 (Box 32)
  - "M" Miscellaneous (1-5 of 6) 1988-1989 (Box 33)
  - "M" Miscellaneous (6 of 6) 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - Marine Science--General 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - Mariners Museum (3 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - Material Management 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - Mathematics--General 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - Medical Center--General (3 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - Medical Center--Personnel (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - Medical Center--Council of Trustees 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - Medical Center--Health Science Council 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - Medical Center--Hospital--General 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - Medical Center--Hospital--Personnel (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - Medical Center--Medical School--General 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - Medical Center--Medical School --Personnel (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - Medical Center--Nursing--General 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - Medical Center--Nursing--Personnel (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - Medical Center--Replacement Hospital Dedication 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - Music--General 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - "N" Miscellaneous (1 of 3) 1988-1989 (Box 36)
  - "N" Miscellaneous (2-3 of 3) 1988-198 (Box 37)
  - New Technology Incorporated (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 37)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges-General (NASULGC) 1988-1989 (Box 38)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges-Committee on International Exchange (NASULGC) 1988-1989 (Box 38)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges-General Circulars (NASULGC) 1988-1989 (Box 38)
  - National Science Foundation 1988-1989 (Box 38)
  - Newcomb Hall--General (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 38)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1988-1989 (Box 38)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities 1988-1989 (Box 38)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa 1988-1989 (Box 38)
  - Online Computer Library Center (OCLC) 1988-1989 (Box 38)
  - "P" Miscellaneous (1 of 4) 1988-1989 (Box 38)
  - "P" Miscellaneous (2-4 of 4) 1988-1989 (Box 39)
  - Parking and Transportation--General 1988-1989 (Box 39)
  - Personnel--General 1988-1989 (Box 39)
  - Personnel and Training (State) 1988-1989 (Box 39)
  - Philosophy--General 1988-1989 (Box 40)
  - Physical Planning--General (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 40)
  - Physical Plant--General 1988-1989 (Box 40)
  - Physical Plant--Project Status Reports (Construction Reports) 1988-1989 (Box 40)
  - Physics--General 1988-1989 (Box 40)
  - Planning and Budget (State)--General 1988-1989 (Box 40)
  - Planning and Budget--Capital Outlay 1988-1989 (Box 40)
  - Planning and Budget-- Medical (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 40)
  - Planning and Budget--University 1988-1989 (Box 40)
  - Poytner Institute 1988-1989 (Box 40)
  - President's Staff Meetings (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 41)
  - Promotions--General 1988-1989 (Box 41)
  - Provost--General 1988-1989 (Box 41)
  - Provost--Associate Provost for Research--General 1988-1989 (Box 41)
  - Psychology--General 1988-1989 (Box 41)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1988-1989 (Box 41)
  - "R" Miscellaneous (1 of 3) 1988-1989 (Box 41)
  - "R" Miscellaneous (2-3 of 3) 1988-1989 (Box 42)
  - Real Estate Foundation--General 1988-1989 (Box 42)
  - Real Estate, Risk Management and Safety--General 1988-1989 (Box 42)
  - Registrar--General 1988-1989 (Box 42)
  - Religious Studies 1988-1989 (Box 42)
  - ROTC--General 1988-1989 (Box 42)
  - ROTC--Air Force 1988-1989 (Box 42)
  - ROTC--Army 1988-1989 (Box 42)
  - ROTC--Navy (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 42)
  - "S" Miscellaneous (1 of 9) 1988-1989 (Box 42)
  - "S" Miscellaneous (2-6 of 9) 1988-1989 (Box 43)
  - "S" Miscellaneous (7-9 of 9) 1988-1989 (Box 44)
  - Senate (University) (1 of 3) 1988-1989 (Box 44)
  - Senate (University) (2-3 of 3) 1988-1989 (Box 45)
  - Salaries--General 1988-1989 (Box 45)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures 1988-1989 (Box 45)
  - Small Business Development Center--General (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 45)
  - Sociology--General 1988-1989 (Box 45)
  - South Africa 1988-1989 (Box 45)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--General 1988-1989 (Box 45)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 45)
  - Southern Regional Education Board--General 1988-1989 (Box 45)
  - Southern Regional Education Board--Publications 1988-1989 (Box 46)
  - Space and Energy Measurement--General (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 46)
  - Spanish, Italian, and Portuguese 1988-1989 (Box 46)
  - Sponsored Programs--General 1988-1989 (Box 46)
  - State Council of Higher Education--General (SCHEV) (3 folders) 1988-1989 Jun (Box 46)
  - State Council of Higher Education--General (SCHEV) (3 folders) 1988 Jul-1989 (Box 47)
  - State Council of Higher Education--Assessment 1988-1989 (Box 47)
  - State Council of Higher Education--Commission on the University of the 21st Century 1988-1989 (Box 47)
  - State Council of Higher Education--Council Notes 1988-1989 (Box 48)
  - State Council of Higher Education--On Line (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 48)
  - State Department of Higher Education--General 1988-1989 (Box 48)
  - State Fire Marshal (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 48)
  - Student Affairs--General (2 folders) 1988-1989 Jun (Box 48)
  - Student Affairs--General 1988 Jul-1989 (Box 48)
  - Student Council--General (1 of 2) 1988-1989 (Box 48)
  - Student Council--General (2 of 2) 1988-1989 (Box 49)
  - Student Council--Minutes 1988-1989 (Box 49)
  - Summer Session 1988-1989 (Box 49)
  - "Ta-Ta" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 49)
  - "Tf-Tz" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 49)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 49)
  - Travel Invoices (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 50)
  - Treasurer (State) (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 50)
  - "U" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 50)
  - United States Savings Bonds--General 1988-1989 (Box 50)
  - United Way--General 1988-1989 (Box 50)
  - Universities Research Association 1988-1989 (Box 50)
  - University Business Innovation Center 1988-1989 (Box 50)
  - University Guides 1988-1989 (Box 51)
  - University Journal 1988-1989 (Box 51)
  - University Police 1988-1989 (Box 51)
  - University Press of Virginia 1988-1989 (Box 51)
  - University Relations 1988-1989 (Box 51)
  - University Union 1988-1989 (Box 51)
  - "V" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 5) 1988-1989 (Box 51)
  - "V" Miscellaneous (3-5 of 5) 1988-1989 (Box 52)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1988-1989 (Box 52)
  - Virginia Festival of American Film (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 52)
  - Virginia Judicial System Commission--Task Force--Alternative Paths to Justice 1988 (Box 53)
  - Virginia Judicial System Commission--Task Force--Mission, Organization, and Administration of Justice 1988 (Box 53)
  - Virginia Judicial System Commission--Task Force--Quality of Justice 1988 (Box 53)
  - Virginia Judicial System Commission--Task Force--Technology of Justice 1988 (Box 53)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review (empty) 1988-1989 (Box 53)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1988-1989 (Box 53)
  - "W" Miscellaneous (1-3 of 6) 1988-1989 (Box 53)
  - "W" Miscellaneous (4-6 of 6) 1988-1989 (Box 54)
  - "X-Y-Z" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 54)
  - GROUP II: Seldom Used Permanent Files
  - Clinch Valley College--Cardwell, Jerry D. 1987-1989 (Box 55)
  - Commerce--Anderson, Joseph V. (Restricted) (5 folders) 1987-1989 (Box 55)
  - Equal Employment--Opportunity/Affirmative Action VII (Restricted) (4 folders) 1987-1988 (Box 55)
  - Lawn Society Meeting 1988 Nov (Box 55)
  - Medical Center--Hospital Advisory Board II--Children's Medical Center Committee (2 folders) 1983-1989 (Box 55)
  - Medical Center--Hospital Advisory Board--Children's Medical Center Committee--Friends Committee I (2 folders) 1985-1988 (Box 55)
  - Miller Center for Public Affairs (2 of 3) 1987 Jul-1988 Jun (Box 55)
  - Miller Center for Public Affairs (3 of 3) 1987 Jul-1988 Jun (Box 56)
  - Minority Affairs (2 folders) 1987 Jul-1988 Jun (Box 56)
  - Physics (SURA)--VIII (3 folders) 1985-1988 (Box 56)
  - Visitors, Board of--General (3 folders) 1987 Jul-1988 Jun (Box 57)
  - Visitors, Board of--Battle, John S., Jr. 1982-1989 (Box 57)
  - Visitors, Board of--Brown, Charles L., Jr. 1986-1989 (Box 57)
  - Visitors, Board of--Camp, William M., Jr. 1982-1989 (Box 57)
  - Visitors, Board of--Cochran, Mrs. George M. 1982-1990 (Box 58)
  - Visitors, Board of--Lewis, Lemuel E. 1986-1990 (Box 58)
  - Visitors, Board of--Smith, Carl W. (2 folders) 1980-1990 (Box 58)
  - Visitors, Board of--Trinkle, James L. (1-3 of 4) 1982-1991 (Box 58)
  - Visitors, Board of--Trinkle, James L. (4 of 4) 1982-1991 (Box 59)
  - Visitors, Board of--White, Wendelin L. (Student) 1989-1990 (Box 59)
- Series III: Ad Hoc Committees
  - Legal Adviser Search--Miscellaneous (Joanne's) 1988-1989 (Box 59)
  - Legal Adviser Search (2 folders) 1987-1989 (Box 59)
  - Legal Adviser Search--Bradshaw, William 1988 (Box 59)
  - Legal Adviser Search--Gottschall, Joan--Legal Adviser Candidate for June 15 and 1988 (Box 59)
  - 17-Jun
  - Legal Adviser Search--Lucas, Laura 1988 (Box 60)
  - Legal Adviser Search--Martin, Roger (Restricted) 1988 (Box 60)
  - Legal Adviser Search--Mingle, James 1986-1988 (Box 60)
  - Legal Adviser Search--Noto, Robert 1988 (Box 60)
  - Legal Adviser Search--Spencer, Mary Y. 1988 (Box 60)
  - Legal Adviser Search--St. Amant, Joseph--Legal Adviser Search II 1988 (Box 60)
  - Legal Adviser Rejects (1-2 of 3) 1988 (Box 60)
  - Legal Adviser Rejects (3 of 3) 1988 (Box 61)
  - Vice President for Business and Finance Research 1988-1989 (Box 61)
  - Vice President for Business and Finance Research--Dahlberg, Kristine M. 1989 (Box 61)
  - Vice President for Business and Finance Research--Madden, Warren (Vice President Business and Finance Candidate) 1989 Apr (Box 61)
  - Vice President for Business and Finance Research--Sandridge, Leonard (2 folders) 1989 (Box 61)
  - Vice President for Business and Finance Research--Stine, Glen R. 1989 (Box 61)
  - Vice President for Business and Finance Research--Williams, Elizabeth 1989 Mar (Box 61)
- Series IV: Administrative Committees
  - Arboretum and Landscape 1988-1989 (Box 61)
  - Athletic Advisory Council 1988-1989 (Box 61)
  - Calendar 1988-1989 (Box 61)
  - University Commencement--Commencement and Convocation 1988 (Box 61)
  - Commencement and Convocation: Subcommittee: Processions 1988-1989 (Box 61)
  - Commencement and Convocation: Subcommittee: Public Occasion 1988-1989 (Box 61)
  - Community Colleges 1988-1989 (Box 61)
  - Computing and Communications 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Development Policy 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Dining Services 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Faculty Benefits 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Financial Aid 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Housing 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - International Students 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Judicial Policy 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Libraries 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Libraries--Subcommittee: Collection Development Policies 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Master Planning Council 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Names 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Proxy Advisory 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Radiation Safety 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Radiation Safety--Subcommittee: Radioactive Drug Res. 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Residential Life 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Traffic Appeals 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Transportation and Parking 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Undergraduate Admissions 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - University Press of Virginia 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - University Research Policy Advisory 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1988-1989 (Box 62)
  - Virginia Status of University Students 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - University Committees--General 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - Rhodes Scholarships 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - Scheduling 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - Security and General Safety 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - Vice Presidents' Committees 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - Ohio State University Foundation 1985 (Box 63)
  - Michigan State University Alumni 1980-1982 (Box 63)
  - University of Washington Foundation 1988 (Box 63)
  - Duke Study (computer diskettes) (2 folders) 1989 (Box 64)
  - Duke University Re-accreditation 1988 (Box 64)
  - Duke University Re-accreditation Report (computer diskette) (1 of 2) 1989 (Box 64)
  - Duke University Re-accreditation Report (2 of 2) 1989 (Box 65)
  - Duke University Re-accreditation Report--(O'Neil Papers) (2 folders) 1989 (Box 65)
- Series V: Robert O'Neil's Speeches
  - List of Speeches 1985-1990 (Box 66)
  - Speeches--Permanent XII (2 folders) 1989 Oct-1990 (Box 66)
  - Speeches--Permanent XI (1-2 of 3 folders) 1989 Feb-Oct (Box 66)
  - Speeches--Permanent XI (3 of 3) 1989 Feb-Oct (Box 67)
  - Speeches--Permanent X (2 folders) 1988 May-1989 Feb (Box 67)
  - Speeches--Permanent IX (2 folders) 1987 Oct-1988 Apr (Box 67)
  - Speeches--Permanent VIII (3 folders) 1987 Jun-Oct (Box 68)
  - Speeches--Permanent VII (2 folders) 1987 Feb-May (Box 68)
  - Speeches--Permanent VI (3 folders) 1986 Sep-1987 Jan (Box 69)
  - Speeches--Permanent V (2 folders) 1986 May-Sep (Box 69)
  - Speeches--Permanent IV (2 folders) 1986 Mar-Apr (Box 70)
  - Speeches--Permanent III (2 folders) 1986 Jan-Mar (Box 70)
  - Speeches--Permanent II (2 folders) 1985 Oct-1986 Jan (Box 71)
  - Speeches--Permanent I (2 folders) 1985 Aug-Oct (Box 71)